【家长提示】本片的评级为 TV-PG-V，可能包含暴力等内容，
因而不建议幼儿独自观赏。
50年过去了
50 years have passed,
我的年岁却没有跟着增长
but I do not age.
时间  再无撼动我一丝一毫
Time has lost its effect on me.
折磨  却从未停止
Yet the suffering continues.
阿蛊的魔爪扼住了过去
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
现在  乃至未来
present, and future.
希望已然消逝
Hope is lost.
必须回去
Gotta get back,
回到过去
back to the past.
杰克武士
Samurai Jack.
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
翻译版本  v1.0.0-CHS
翻译  妙挖種子
校对  SerCom_KC
真是太不可思议了！
Incredible.
我们先去吃东西吧
We should eat.
等会儿要坐很久的
This is going to be a long journey.
看起来好好吃的样子
This looks good.
你以前吃过这东西吗？
Have you had it before?
当然吃过
Yes, of course.
还吃过很  很多次
Many, many times.
就是  我吃过一些跟这差不多的
Or something very similar.
嗯  嗯  都是好东西
Yah, yah, all very good.
都是对你们好的东西
Very good for you.
是吧  你也可以吃
See? It is even good for you.
特别是这个
This one especially.
Mmm, mmm.
嗯  好吃
Mmm. Delicious.
来  尝一个
Please, have some.
不了  我就不用了  哈
No! Thank you, heh.
我还是去那边看看吧
I'll just try something over here.
真是  女人心海底针啊  你说是吧？
Woman -- who understands them, yah?
嗯  大概
Yes... I guess.
总感觉有点不舒服啊
I don't feel so good.
是不是我刚吃什么吃坏了？
Maybe it was something I ate?
应该是了
Yeah, that might be it.
啊  现在好多了
Ah, that's better.
借个位啊
Excuse me.
不好意思啊
Pardon me.
稍微有点…挤呢
It's a little, uh... crowded.
嗯
Yes.
啊  有东西顶到了
Oh! Something's poking me.
噢！对不起
Oh! I'm so sorry.
抱歉  我…
Sorry, I --
不  是我…
No, I --
这有点好笑啊
That was quite humorous,
我们这么抓着杆子
the way we were trying to grab the pole
结果我们的手总是…碰到一起
but our hands kept... touching.
Ha ha... ha.
好像有点儿开始变热了
The temperature seems to be rising.
（去死）
（死亡）
阿喜…
Ashi...
（去死  杰克武士）
有情况
... we are not alone.
噢  不好意思  我…
Oh! Sorry, I --
不  是我的错
No, I -- I'm sorry!
我没有注意到你！
I didn't see you!
小心！
Look out!
我们是不是离开这里会比较好
Should we leave, perhaps?
嗯  我觉得这样不错
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
（哇！）
喂！
Hey!
我们得找个地方避一避！
We have to find some shelter!
哪边？
Where?!
Aah!
前面那个是什么啊
What is that?!
看那里！
There!
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
我也说不清
I don't know.
但这地方确实挺大
But it is big.
阿喜  小心…
Ashi, be care--
…点
--ful.
刚刚你说什么？
Did you say something?
没什么
No.
当我没说
Never mind.
好像是某种文字
Some kind of writing.
看上面
Look up.
非常狭窄的空间
Very confined space.
应该是监狱了
This is some kind of prison.
监狱？
Prison?
但是囚犯哪儿去了？
But where are its prisoners?
Aaah!
没事吧？
Are you all right?
开始扩散了！
It's spreading!
到底是什么啊
What was that?
不知道  但我们最好离开这里
I don't know, but we should leave.
前面应该就是我们进来的地方了
The way we came in should be up ahead.
不是吧
Oh, no.
明明就在这里的啊
It should've been right here.
我们不能呆在这里！
We have to keep going!
杰克  抱歉  我…
Jack, I'm sorry, I --
不  你不用道歉  我也觉得应该是这里
No, please, I thought it was this way, also.
这地方到底是搞什么啊？
What madness is this?
管它是什么  总比被追上了要好
I'll choose this over whatever is chasing us.
我们迷路了
We're lost!
只能继续往前走了！
We have to keep moving!
这里还有一间牢房啊
It's another prison cell.
嗯  而且这个还很大
Yes, a very big one.
关押在这里的大概就是那东西了吧
And I'm afraid its occupant has returned.
阿喜  小心！
Ashi, look out!
赶紧离开这里吧
We got to get out of here!
同感
I agree.
开始扫描
Scan initiated.
检测到非囚禁对象生命体
Non-prisoner life-forms detected.
准许进入
Access granted.
检测到多个牢房已被突破
Multiple prison-cell breach detected.
启动压制协议
Containment protocol initiated.
第三象限  检测到突破
Quadrant III -- breach detected.
囚禁对象  拉撒路-92
Prisoner Lazarus-92.
极度危险的复构可再生有机体
Extremely dangerous multiple regenerating organism.
紧急协议指南如下
Emergency protocol instructions.
无效化武器型号X-49
Neutralizing weapon model X-49.
待拉撒路-92进入武器范围后
Once Lazarus-92 has entered the weapon vicinity,
武器的启动顺序按以下步骤进行
weapon sequence initiating directions follow.
第一步…
Step one --
抱歉
Sorry.
只有按上述正确的武器启动序列进行操作
And only after that proper weapon initializing sequence
才能消灭拉撒路-92
can Lazarus-92 be terminated.
等等  什么？！
Wait. What?!
以上为拉撒路协议的全部内容
Lazarus protocol concluded.
别  等等啊  我还…
No, please, I --
可是  到底要怎么启动啊？
But how does one initiate it?
我准备好了
I am ready.
我也…
As am I...
那是什么东西？
What is that?
这个  是专门用来消灭那个怪物的武器
Well, it is a weapon designed specifically to kill the creature.
太好了
Excellent.
嗯…
Yes...
走吧
Let's go.
来了
It's coming.
把武器准备好
Get ready the weapon.
好…
Yes...
趁现在  杰克！
Now, Jack!
杰克？杰克？
Jack? Jack?
为什么不用武器？
Why aren't you using the weapon?!
我…不知道要怎么用！
I... don't know how to use it!
什么？！
What?!
有一个特定的启动序列  但我不知道是什么
There's an initiating sequence, and I do not know it!
让我试试？
Maybe I can try?
呃  好吧…
Um, okay...
阿喜  接！
Ashi, catch!
怎么了？
What's wrong?!
我也不会弄！
I can't get it to work!
阿喜  你没穿衣服！
Ashi, you're naked!
所以呢？
So?
嗯  这个  你看啊
Well, I mean, you know,
首先男女有别  而且…
men and women are different and...
自己的东西是私密
private things are personal.
我不知道你想说什么！
You're not making any sense!
杰克！
Jack!
你这是干什么？
What are you doing?
呃  在怪物面前要保护好自己
Uh, you need protection from the creature.
就凭你的长袍？
And your robe is gonna protect me?
那个叫做着  还有  没错！
Actually it's a gi. And, yes!
ぎ
※在日语中，「着」一般作为后缀，例如「柔道着」（じゅうどうぎ，柔道服）
或「空手着」（からてぎ，空手道服）。在英语中，“gi”泛指武术服装。
总感觉你突然变得怪怪的
You're acting weird.
说我怪？
Me? Weird?
我怪吗？哈哈  哈！
Me?! Ha ha! Ha!
好吧
Okay...
你想干嘛？
What are you doing?
只能这样了
It is the only way.
我必须得试出来
I have to try.
尽量掩护我  越久越好
Cover me for as long as you can!
杰克！
J-a-a-ack!
我快撑不住了！
I can't hold it anymore!
序列已启动
Sequence initiated.
Aaaaah!
杰克！
Jack!
阿喜！
Ashi!
Aaaah!
♪ Dean Martin - Everybody Loves Somebody ♪
Everybody loves somebody sometime
每个人都会在某个时刻坠入爱河
Everybody falls in love somehow
每个人都会在不知不觉中坠入爱河
Something in your kiss just told me
我从你的吻中感受到了
My sometime is now
现在就是那个时刻
Everybody finds somebody someplace
每个人都会在某个地方坠入爱河
There's no tellin' where love may appear
没人知道爱情会在何处悄然降临
第玖拾玖集
Something in my heart keeps sayin'
我从内心深处感受到了
My someplace is here
这里就是那个地方
If I had it in my power
倘若我有这样的能力
I'd arrange for every girl to have your charms
我想让所有女孩都能拥有你的魅力
Then, every minute...
如此一来  每一分…